leapmotion.com 2013-04-28

# Leap Motion

This Leap Motion privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you of Leap Motion Inc.'s ("we," "us," or "our") policies and practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information through the Leap Motion Site and Leap Motion Services. We define Personal Information as information that allows someone to identify or contact you, including for example your name, address, telephone number, and email address.

By registering with us or using our website, you expressly consent to the information handling practices in this privacy policy. If you reside outside the United States, you understand that your personal information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing personal information may be less stringent than in your country.

This Privacy Policy is a part of our Terms of Use. If any term of this Privacy Policy is inconsistent or conflicts with any term of the Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy will control. Capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy but not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given to them in the Terms of Use.

## Personal Information You Provide to us

When you register to use Leap Motion Services, we may collect your name, e-mail address and e-mail preferences, and password for your account. We may also ask you to provide additional information on an optional basis in connection with setting up your account. You may also register by using your log-in credentials from social networking websites, including Facebook, Twitter, or LinkedIn. When you register in this way, we may collect Personal Information from the social networking websites that you have given us permission to collect or made publicly available. The information Leap Motion obtains may depend on your privacy settings with the social networking website. When you purchase any Materials or services from the Leap Motion Site, we may collect your name, phone number, e-mail address, mailing address, billing address, complete credit card information that enables us to receive your payment (however we do not retain your credit card number unless requested) and federal tax identification number or European Union VAT number as applicable. When you give us feedback, we may collect any information that is contained in your feedback. When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, fax, or letter, we collect your e-mail address, fax number, or mailing address, and any information contained in the e-mail, fax, or letter you send us.

## Personal Information Collected via Technology

As you use the Leap Motion Site or any Leap Motion Service, some information may also be collected passively, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, access time, mobile phone model, and telecom carrier. We may also store a small text file called a "Cookie" on your computer or phone to store certain information about your use of the Leap Motion Site or Leap Motion Services. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer or phone until you delete them). We may collect and store information locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage and application data caches.

So that Leap Motion can provide services, such as version upgrades and app recommendations, we may passively collect information that identifies your mobile device, such as the International Mobile Equipment Identity, IP address, and Android ID. Leap Motion may also automatically collect data about apps you have installed and the frequency of their use. We may collect details of how you used the Leap Motion Services, such as your browsing behaviors and search queries.

## Use of Information

We use your Personal Information to provide the Leap Motion Services to you, to respond to requests that you make, to personalize your online experience on the Leap Motion Site, to improve the Leap Motion Site and Leap Motion Services, and to better tailor the features, performance, and support of the Leap Motion Services.

We may use your Personal Information to send you electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails, unless you have requested not to receive such promotional communications from us. We may also use your Personal Information to send you Leap Motion Services-related communications, and you may opt out of these communications if you terminate your account.

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information. We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information at our discretion. "Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information.

Any feedback you provide will be governed by the Terms of Use.

## Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share your Personal Information with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so. We may provide your Personal Information to specified third parties for sending you promotional e-mails relating to such third parties' products, unless you have requested us not to receive promotional communications from such third parties.

We may provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide the Leap Motion Site and Leap Motion Services. However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information (except pursuant to a legal requirement such as a subpoena or warrant). 

We may provide your credit card and related billing and payment information to third party service providers engaged on Leap Motion's behalf, including payment processors and/or credit agencies, for the purposes of checking credit, effecting payment, and servicing your accounts. These Providers may store your credit card information using PCI compliant security practices for the purposes of facilitating enhanced ordering of Leap Motion devices or applications. 

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our Affiliates in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

We will not share any Personal Information with any of our app developer partners.

If we or our assets related to this Privacy Policy are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Law Enforcement Compliance

We may be required by law, or by law enforcement officers acting under the color of law, to record some or all of your communications on or through the Leap Motion Site or Leap Motion Services. We may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information (including your account information) and your communications through the Leap Motion Site and Leap Motion Services, if required by law or by law enforcement officers acting under the color of law, or if we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to: (1) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (2) to protect and defend ours, our Affiliates,' other users,' or your, rights, property or safety.

Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us or the Leap Motion Site, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive.

Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you administrative e-mails regarding the Leap Motion Service, including, for example, purchase confirmation, account creation confirmation, and notices of material changes to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

You may change your email address and password for the Service by editing it in your account page. You may request deletion of your Personal Information by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request, only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.

## Regarding Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about Users who are under the age of 13.

Third Party Sites, Third Party Services, and Third Party Materials

Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to Third Party Sites, Third Party Services or Third Party Materials that have links or are provided through the Leap Motion Site. Third party providers of such Third Party Sites, Third Party Services or Third Party Materials, may collect (via tracking technologies like Cookies or web beacons) and use Anonymous Information regarding your interaction with the Third Party Sites, Third Party Services or Third Party Materials that they deliver and with which you interact.

## Security

We make reasonable efforts to protect your Personal information, but no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks connected to handling information on the internet.

## Privacy Policy Updates

This Privacy Policy may be amended at any time in accordance with the section titled "Updates" in the [Terms of Use].

## Contacting Leap Motion

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact Leap Motion in the following ways:

### Web

<https://www.leapmotion.com/contact>

### Postal

Leap Motion, Inc.

333 Bryant St,

Suite LL150

San Francisco, CA 94107

U.S.A.

### Phone

+1 415 689 5212
